const data = [
{
    question: 'Who is the winningest driver of all time?',
    answers: [
        'Lewis Hamilton',
        'Sebastian Vettel',
        'Michael Schumacher',
        'Aryton Senna'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Michael Schumacher'
},

{
    question: 'How many world championships does Michael Schumacher have?',
    answers: [
        '4',
        '7',
        '8',
        '10'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '7'
},

{
    question: 'This driver won the drivers world championship 4 years in a row from 2010-2013',
    answers: [
        'Sebastian Vettel',
        'Lewis Hamilton',
        'Fernando Alonso',
        'Nico Rosberg'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Sebastian Vettel'
},

{
    question: 'Who was the youngest driver to start a formula 1 race?',
    answers: [
        'Michael Schumacher',
        'Max Verstappen',
        'Lance Stroll',
        'Lewis Hamilton'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Max Verstappen'
},

{
    question: 'Who holds the record for most pole positions?',
    answers: [
        'Michael Schumacher',
        'Aryton Senna',
        'Sebastian Vettel',
        'Lewis Hamilton'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Lewis Hamilton'
},
{
    question: 'What is the oldest team in Formula 1? (years active)',
    answers: [
        'Mercedes',
        'Ferrari',
        'WIlliams',
        'Haas'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ferrari'
},
{
    question: 'What team won the 2018 Formula 1 season?',
    answers: [
        'Mercedes',
        'Redbull',
        'Ferrari',
        'Toro Rosso'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Mercedes'
},
{
    question: 'How many years in a row has Mercedes won the Formula 1 world championship?',
    answers: [
        '2',
        '3',
        '4',
        '5'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '5'
},
{
    question: 'What is the name of the only team based in the Unitied States?',
    answers: [
        'Redbull',
        'Haas',
        'Williams',
        'Renault'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Haas'
},
{
    question: 'What is the fastest recorded speed for a formula 1 car?',
    answers: [
        '204.7mph',
        '216.8mph',
        '231.5mph',
        '243.2mph'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '231.5mph'
}

];